So I have two folds, so I should get two sets of training times,
我有两个折 因此我应该有
predicting times, and accuracies.
两组训练时间、预测时间和精确度
See, it only takes a few seconds to do the training and predicting, but
进行训练和预测只用了几秒钟时间
the accuracy is really terrible, less than 1% on my first fold and
但精确度则问题很严重
only 15% on my second fold.
第一折不到 1% 第二折只有 15%
So what on Earth might be going on here?
那么这里到底发生了什么？
To help unpack this, I'm going to add a couple of print statements to this.
为帮助弄清楚原因 我将在此处添加几个打印语句
The first thing that I'm going to do is I'm going to actually look
我要做的第一件事就是
at the indices of all of the events that are going into my training data set.
查看训练数据集中的所有事件的指数是否
Are there any patterns where all of a particular type of event end up in
存在着这种情况
the training data set, and
即所有某一特定的事件类型最后都属于训练数据集
all of a particular other type of event end up in the testing data set?
而所有另一特定的事件类型最后都属于测试数据集？
because if that's the case, then I shouldn't expect that training on
因为如果存在着这种情况 我不会认为
one type of event allows me to classify very well another type of event.
针对一种类型事件的训练会帮助我成功地对另一种类型的事件进行分类
The other thing I'll also do is print out
另一件我要做的事情是
the labels of all of the events that are in my training data set.
打印出训练数据集中所有事件的标签
So this is repeating some similar information, but
这样会重复某些相似的信息
now I'm looking at the labels directly.
但现在我就可以直接查看标签了
And last, I'll print out the authors of the testing data set
最后 我要打印出测试数据集里的作者
to see if there's some important difference between the events that
来查看训练数据集和测试数据集中的事件
are going into the training data set and the testing data set.
是否有某些重要的区别
Ha, so we get a lot of output because I have thousands of events.
这样我们会获得大量输出 因为我有数千个事件
Let me go back up to the first line.
我要返回到第一行
This line here is showing me the indices of all of the data that's going
该行显示我的训练数据集中
into my training data set, and
所有数据的指数
I can see that what it's doing here is it's just counting sequentially.
而且我发现它的作用仅仅是按顺序计数
So all of the events from 8,789 until the end of the data set,
也就是说 从 8,789 到数据集末尾的 17,577
17,577, are going into the training data set.
都将进入训练数据集
The other half that go from 1 to 8,789,
从 1 到 8,789 的另一半则会
those are all going to the testing data set.
全部进入测试数据集
So in other words, I'm not shuffling my events around at all.
换句话说 我根本没有把事件顺序打乱
I'm not doing any randomization.
我没有做任何随机化
I'm just splitting my data set into two pieces, right down the middle.
我只是将我的数据集从中间分成两部分
And as it happens, there's a pattern in my data set that this will mess up.
刚巧我的数据集中有一种模式会把结果搞乱
The pattern happens to be that all of my emails from Sarah are in the first half
这种模式是
of the data set.
Sarah 发给我的所有电子邮件都在数据集的第一部分
And all of my e-mails from Chris are in the second half of the data set.
而 Chris 发给我的所有电子邮件都在数据集的第二部分
And this becomes immediately clear when I start looking at the labels that
当我查看测试和训练数据集上显示的标签时
are showing up in the testing and the training data set.
立即就发现了这一情况
So, all of these ones right here are the labels of the items
所有这些都是
in the training data set.
训练数据集中项目的标签
You can see everything that's in the training data set is of class 1.
你会发现 训练数据集中的所有内容都属于类别 1
Then I start a second list.
然后我开始创建第二个列表
These are the labels of all of the items that are in the testing data set.
这是测试数据集中所有项目的标签
I can see that everything that's in the testing data set is of label 0.
我发现测试数据集中的所有内容标签都是 0
And then I have maybe a few 1s at the very end.
然后可能在最后有若干个 1
So what's happening is I'm doing all my training on the emails from one person
实际情况就是 我通过一个人发来的电子邮件进行各项训练
and then using them to try to classify emails from the second person.
然后利用这些信息对第二个人发来的电子邮件进行分类
This is like training a machine learning algorithm to drive a car and
这就好像训练机器学习算法开车
then asking it to cook you breakfast.
然后要求它做早饭
It's not going to work.
这样是不行的
So, and this is a feature, I would say,
我觉得这是
of how the sklearn KFold algorithm works.
sklearn KFold 算法的工作原理
Is it's just going to split the data sort of into equal sized partitions.
只是将数据划分为大小相同的两部分
It's not going to perform any type of shuffling of the events.
不会对事件进行任何类型的乱排序
So if there's patterns in the way that the classes, especially, are represented
如果你的数据里的表现方式上 尤其是类别上 存在某些模式
in your data, then these patterns are going to be reflected in sort of
然后这些模式会反映在大量特定的标签中
big lumps of certain labels, ending up in particular folds of your validation.
最终会体现在验证的特定折上
This is probably not what you want.
这可能不是你想看到的